astanda.com 2012-10-03

# 

Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

Astanda.com is committed to providing its users with an Internet experience that respects and protects their personal privacy choices and concerns. Our privacy policy believes in honesty, openness, and fair play in its dealings with all users. Users have equal opportunities, regardless of sex, race, color, religion, age or national origin. Information in the user file will not be verified or released to anyone out-side Astanda.com, its agents or representatives, unless Astanda.com is required by legal proccess to provide information. 

Our affiliates have their own privacy policy statements, which we encourage you to read whenever you visit their sites. When we talk about "Astanda.com" or "we" in this policy, we are referring to Astanda.com group and its majority-owned or majority-controlled subsidiaries. 

Personally identifiable information is information-such as your name, birth date, e-mail address or mailing address-that can be used to uniquely identify you.  
Anonymous Information is not personally identifiable information. Anonymous information is information about how you use our site (such as places visited and search queries performed). Anonymous information also includes the domain names of browsers that visit our site, time of day the site was visited, and other non-personally identifiable information. Anonymous information is information that is not tied to any individual, but helps to characterize Astanda.com's users (for example, the average unique hits to our download area over 30 minutes). 

We want to assure you that you can visit our site and use many of our services without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself to us. It is only during registration to become a registered user will you be asked to provide us (and/or our affiliates) with personally identifiable information. Although the majority of our services do not require any form of customer registration, we do require registration for the use of certain services, e.g., Support Forums. During this registration process we require you to complete certain fields, and ask you to select a user name and password. 

From time to time, we may run contests on our site in which we ask participants for contact information, such as their email address(es). If you participate in contests, your contact information will be used primarily to reach you in connection with the contests. 

When you use our site, we collect anonymous information, even if you have not registered with Astanda.com (for a contest, or for any Astanda.com service). We use this information to personalize your experience at our site, show you more relevant advertising messages, and generally to improve our services. We share this anonymous information with selected advertisers and partners in order to deliver to you more relevant advertising messages. Astanda.com will not share any anonymous information about your use if that information is or might be linked to your personally identifiable information.
